With Ren, that sort of next step is impossible.
I never expected us to be more than friends.
Why are you like this, Kinoshita?
I'm only nice to girls I like.
I'm the one who decided I would go along with my dad.
This is good bye.
No feelings last forever, do they?
I won't leave you.
I'll always be here for you.
I have to shut these feelings up inside me.
I can't ever expect anything more.
[Spring, 2 Years Ago]
What're you doing out alone so late at night?
You should be heading home.
[Hajime Moriya]
Any reason why you're not?
Well...
Daiki!
There you are.
I was waiting for my younger brother.
Get home safe, alright? It's getting dark out.
- We will.
- Yeah.
Sorry, but I'm not Daiki.
I know you're not.
Sorry to get you involved in all that.
You shouldn't be out alone at night. It can be dangerous.
I actually live in that apartment down the hill.
I just don't want to settle down there.
I moved there with my mother,
but I know my family won't stay apart forever.
It's not like my parents got divorced or anything.
I see.
She's here again.
Ren?
I hope your family gets back together soon.
Look at you, trying to act all mature.
I'm only two years younger than you.
My parents are getting divorced.
I'll be moving out of that temporary apartment with my mother.
Thanks for always keeping me company.
You don't need to put on a brave face with me.
Let yourself be honest.
It wasn't that long ago...
when the whole family was happy together.
When we enjoyed each other's company.
I wonder if the time we shared was all a lie.
When did it all come crashing down?
My parents promised eternal love to each other.
But I guess no feelings last forever, do they?
I'll stay with you.
Always.
I'll prove to you some things won't ever change.
- Another year has come and gone.
- It sure has.
Have you already applied to work part-time elsewhere?
No, not yet.
In that case, would you like to continue working here?
I know I originally hired you to help with the grand opening rush,
but you've been a real big help to the cafe.
I would love to continue working here.
Really? Thanks, I'm glad you're sticking around.
Will everyone else be staying on the team as well?
Well, about that...
Welcome in, Kashiwagi.
I'm ready for my first shift.
[Ritsuko Kashiwagi]
We're excited to have you. Right this way.
Go lend Kinoshita a hand for me, will you?
I still have things to finish up here.
Could you help Kinoshita instead?
Manabu?
Huh?
Right, sure.
- I'm here to help.
- Thanks.
Was that our new part-timer?
That's right.
She'll be filling in for Ren since he's quitting soon.
What?
Kyo didn't want to see him go either, so it's too bad.
What's up?
I confessed to Ninako.
And you're reporting this to me because?
Because I want to see what you'll do.
You notice what's going on in there, don't you?
What are you talking about?
How about you become my rival?
There's no reason for us to be rivals.
Ando.
I already have my answer.
I'm not second-guessing myself.
[Episode 5]
I was making decisions on my own, without hearing you out.
I'm sorry.
I was only trying to act mature.
The truth is, I don't want us to break up at all.
Please, give me another chance.
I'm giving this back to you.
It's a Christmas present, right?
Then you have to give it to me on Christmas day.
Am I wrong?
Daiki.
Don't jump to conclusions on your own, okay?
I don't care if you think you'll look lame.
Just tell me how you really feel.
And Daiki?
Let's figure out what works, together.
That's what I want for the both of us.
What about you, Daiki?
Daiki decided he'd stay here with his mother and sister.
He was finally able to be honest with his father.
Not bad, Daiki.
I've made my choice, too.
I'll stand by Daiki's side, hand-in-hand, as equals.
I wouldn't want to repeat my mistakes, after all.
The last guy I dated was a classmate from middle school.
He was incredibly kind, and always went along with my whims.
His thoughtfulness became the norm for me.
And then, another girl stole him from right under my nose.
What?
That's when I realized something really important.
A relationship that expects too much from one party,
will never end well.
Let's break.
Thank you.
- Great work, everyone.
- You too.
Mayuka, your cover shot for the August issue was beautiful.
Thanks.
- Sakura, you're up next.
- Okay.
[Aki Takazawa]
The questionnaire for next month's issue.
Fill it in when you have time, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
[February Issue Questionnaire]
[Mannerisms you find cute in boys?]
So your boyfriend touches his collarbone
when he feels embarrassed?
[When they touch their collarbone...]
That's a bit too specific, don't you think?
I suppose so.
Say, are you free on December 24th?
- I'm sorry, but...
- There's an audition for a commercial,
and the client insists on having you.
I'll be there.
Are you... sure?
You don't need to apologize.
Don't worry about it, I'm the one with the flexible schedule.
You just keep studying and working as you need to, alright?
Talk to you later.
I see we're on the same train again.
Seems like it.
So you're quitting the part-time job?
Yeah.
I'm trying to make more time for Mayuka now.
I heard the news from Daiki.
I'm sure Mayuka will be okay.
You're there to help her through this tough time.
Yeah.
No matter how much I love Ren,
there will never be room for me in between their relationship.
You'll only learn to feel oppressed by that reality.
Those are the limits I'm talking about.
Christmas is coming up.
Do you have plans with Mayuka?
Yeah.
We've got plans.
I see.
I hope you two enjoy your time together.
Something's off about Ren's smile today.
I hope I was only imagining things.
We sure are getting loads of couples today.
I'm not surprised.
It's Christmas Eve, after all.
- Say, Ninako.
- Yeah?
Do you have a crush?
I do.
It's no one you know though.
- I see.
- Yeah.
- Excuse me.
- One moment.
Gacchan, you have a crush on Ninako?
No? I was just wondering if she still had a thing for Ren.
I like Ren when he's with Ninako.
So you're on his side too?
Of course I am.
I envy you, Gacchan. You seem to have no worries at all.
You're not the first to say that.
No person is without worry though.
I have to work until closing today...
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
Hey there.
Hey.
You've got a tough heart, don't you?
I mean, your crush is probably enjoying
a Christmas date right now.
I'd lose my appetite at the thought.
Unlike you, I'm a sensitive guy at heart.
Don't compare your pathetic stomach to mine.
And what are those boney wrists?
I bet you're even lankier than me.
Oh yeah? There's no way.
Really? Then prove it.
- Ready, and...
Dang it, I lost.
I'm not holding your hand.
Remember when you said I'd face my limits soon enough?
I think I'm coming to realize what you were talking about.
Then choose me.
If I was your boyfriend, I would cherish you.
I would treasure you.
I would make you fall for me.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
How was your first ever Christmas date?
Can it. How did your audition go?
It was perfect.
Oh? Guess it was worth choosing your job over Ichinose, huh?
Don't put it like that.
Man, if I were Ichinose, I'd be crying waterfalls about now.
Ren understands how important my job is to me.
He's just trying to be the mature one.
Men like to look good in front of girls.
Don't chalk up your attitude as a universal experience.
Besides, Ren isn't a brat like you.
I'm impressed.
Ichinose manages to act like the mature adult for you, huh?
I'm sorry I had to cancel today.
You don't need to apologize.
Where should we go when your exams are over?
Let's visit someplace you've been dying to go to.
Together, of course.
I'll be by your side, okay?
Always.
Thanks.
Talk to you soon.
- I'm going to hop in the car.
- Sure.
Dad, why did you get a divorce with Mom?
If you were only going to part ways,
you shouldn't have married her at all.
I know you may not be convinced,
especially when it's coming from me.
But everything I promised your mother back then,
was truly how I felt about her.
Are you that shocked about Dad remarrying?
No. I'm more shocked at how I'm okay with it.
So you've accepted it after all.
The same breeze rustles our hair.
Yet something about that...
is endearing to me.
Ren.
Thanks for all you've done for me.
Huh?
You'd always cover for my slip ups at the cafe. So, thank you.
It was no big deal, really.
- I forgot something at the cafe, so I need to head back.
- Sure.
Have a happy new year.
You too.
I could continue pining for Ren,
and keep piling on reasons to love him.
But it would only hurt in the end.
- Ando.
- Ninako?
Can we talk?
[Season 1 Finale]
I knew nothing about this feeling a year ago.
I love you. I really do.
Plenty of things will remain the same though.
Why does it become so complicated when like turns to love?
I want to stay in love with Ren.
[Epilogue]
Ren, don't quit the job. Please?
I told you, I already turned in my final notice.
Then could you at least tell me why you're quitting?
Because the grand opening rush is coming to an end.
Doesn't that suffice for a reason?
I'm asking because I think there's more to it than that.
Don't be stubborn and deny how you really feel.
Manabu.
Am I really acting in the wrong here?
What's so bad about being stubborn?
I told you not to stir the pot, and make his life more confusing.
But Ninako's the one he really...
Which is exactly why he's distancing himself.
He's doing his best to extinguish his feelings for her.
That's the answer he settled on, alright?